Kevin Gerstner

Game Developer, Web Developer

kevingerstner.com Sirkevinicus@gmail.com

github.com/SirKevinicus

314-614-2301

Work Experience

Graphic Design Intern @ ArchCity Defenders

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019 \\ SAINT LOUIS, MO

- Made digital art recreation of clients using Photoshop for 10th Anniversary print and web marketing.
- Created social media graphics, one of which got over 300 shares on Facebook.
- Researched social justice issues and communicated key issues to the affected communities.

Research Assistant @ University of Tulsa

OCT 2018 - APR 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Researched, co-authored and published a paper with Prof. Sandeep Kuttal entitled: "Remote Pair-Programming in Online CS Education: Investigating through a Gender Lens", which was presented in the 2019 VL/HCC (Visual Languages & Human Centric Computing) conference.

Game Navigator & Server @ Shuffles Board Game Café

SEP 2018 - JAN 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Taught parties of people how to play board games, as well as taking orders and delivering food. In my spare time, I read rule books to learn new games.

Projects

Portfolio Website kevingerstner.com

Web Developer \\ 2021

- » Designed and coded a portfolio website using HTML, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap 5, and JS
- Used Netlify to host and Namecheap for domain
- Worked with web-friendly standards like Responsive Design, WEBM/P files, and Lighthouse

Tomb of Khaibit BLU3 J3LLO Studios

Environment Designer & Tools Programmer \\ 2021

- » Created a Unity editor tool called Texo that can make procedurally generated roguelike dungeons
- Made pixel art for the tomb environment using Aseprite

Song Pong NULLVALU_Studios

Feature Developer & Artist \\ 2020

- Made a rhythm game inspired by the 80s and Pong in three months with the Unity engine
- Coded features like spawning notes along to the beat and a song editor
- Created art assets in Illustrator and Blender

Knock-Out! Global Smackdown Board Game Interactive Jeans

Board Game Designer & Artist \\ 2018

- » Created over 150 unique card artworks, box art, and graphics for marketing
- >> Created a Wordpress website
- Launched a Kickstarter campaign

Summary

Passionate, well-rounded developer and designer with experience creating C# games in Unity and websites with HTML, SASS, and JS. Will graduate in 2021 with BS Computer Science / Art & Math Minor. Excellent at working with a team to implement ideas to create a finished product. Picks up new skills quickly.

Programming Languages

HTML · CSS/SASS · JavaScript · C# · Java

Tools & Platforms

GitHub · Netlify · WordPress · ClickUp Webflow

Design

Photoshop · Illustrator · InDesign · Figma · Aseprite

Education

University of Tulsa 2017 - 2021 \\ TULSA, OK

B.S. in Computer Science and B.S. in Computer Simulation and Gaming

with Math and Art minors

Interests

Board Games, Overwatch, Art, Animated movies, Horror Games